Guide to the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), New York Local Records WAG.282
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Negotiations
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: ABC for 1960-1963 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: ABC for 1963-1966 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: ABC for 1973-1976, 1973-1975 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: ABC for 1976-1979 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: ABC for 1979-1982 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: ABC for 1979-1982, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: ABC for 1979-1982, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: ABC for 1982-1985, Jan-Sep 1982 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: ABC for 1982-1985, Oct-Dec 1982 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: ABC for 1982-1985, Jan-Jun 1983 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: ABC for 1982-1985, Jul-Dec 1983 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: ABC for 1982-1985, 1984-1985 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: ABC for 1982-1986 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: ABC Correspondence and Related Materials, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - [Network] Television [and Radio] Broadcasting: ABC Correspondence and Related Materials, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - [Network] Television [and Radio] Broadcasting: ABC Correspondence and Related Materials, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - [Network] Television [and Radio] Broadcasting: ABC Correspondence and Related Materials, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - [Network] Television [and Radio] Broadcasting: ABC Correspondence and Related Materials, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - [Network] Television [and Radio] Broadcasting: ABC Correspondence and Related Materials, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - [Network] Television [and Radio] Broadcasting: ABC Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: ABC, "The Dick Clark Beech-Nut Show" Production Memoranda, 1959 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: ABC, "Good Morning America" Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: ABC, "Good Morning America" Correspondence, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: CBS for 1963-1966 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: CBS for 1966-1969 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: CBS for 1969-1972 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: CBS for 1969-1972, "Caught in the Middle", 1970-1972 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: CBS for 1972-1974, 1973-1974 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: CBS for 1974-1976, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: CBS for 1976-1979 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: CBS for 1976-1979, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: CBS for 1976-1979, 1978-1979 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: CBS for 1979-1982, 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: CBS for 1979-1982, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: CBS for 1982-1985 (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: CBS for 1985-1988, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: CBS "Ed Sullivan Show" Production Memoranda, 1957 (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: Dumont, "The Plainclothes Man" Production Memoranda, 1952-1954 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: [From Binder] for 1976-1979, Part I, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: [From Binder] for 1976-1979, Part II, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: [From Binder] for 1976-1979, Part III, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: [From Binder] for 1979-1982, Part I, 1979-1980 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: [From Binder] for 1979-1982, Part II, 1979-1980 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: [From Binder] for 1979-1982, Part III, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: [From Binder] for 1979-1982, Part IV, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - [Network] Television [and Radio] Broadcasting: [From Binder] for 1979-1982, Part I, 1979-1981 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - [Network] Television [and Radio] Broadcasting: [From Binder] for 1979-1982, Part II (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - [Network] Television [and Radio] Broadcasting: [From Binder] for 1979-1982, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: [From Binder] for 1982-1985 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: [From Binder] for 1982-1985, General Provisions, Part I, 1983 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: [From Binder] for 1982-1985, General Provisions, Part II, 1983 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: [From Binder] for 1982-1985, General Provisions, Additional Materials, 1983 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: FOX for 1985-1988, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: NBC for 1963-1966, 1963-1965 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: NBC for 1966-1969, 1967-1969 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: NBC for 1969-1972 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: NBC for 1973-1976, 1973-1974 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: NBC for 1973-1976, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: NBC for 1973-1976 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: NBC for 1976-1979, 1975-1976 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: NBC for 1976-1979, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: NBC for 1976-1979, 1978-1979 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: NBC for 1976-1979, Local News (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: NBC for 1979-1982 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: NBC for 1979-1982, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: NBC for 1979-1982, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: NBC for 1982-1985 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: NBC for 1982-1985, 1983-1985 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: NBC for 1985-1988, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: NBC "Today Show" Production Memoranda, 1958-1959 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: Reference Guide, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - [Network] Television Broadcasting: Supplemental Markets, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Television News, Inc. (TVN) for 1973-1975, 1973-1976 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: AFTRA-SAG Negotiations, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: AFTRA-SAG Negotiations, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Campbell-Ewald Company Correspondence and Penalty Provision, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Contracts, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Correspondence, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Television [and Radio] Recorded Commercials: Correspondence re. Composers, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Freelance Performers, 1974-1975 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Television [and Radio] Recorded Commercials: Interim Agreement, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Television [and Radio] Recorded Commercials: Interim Agreement, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected [From Binder], A, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected [From Binder], B, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected [From Binder], C, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected [From Binder], D, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected [From Binder], E-F, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected [From Binder], G, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected [From Binder], H-J, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected [From Binder], K-L, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected [From Binder], M, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected [From Binder], N-Q, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected [From Binder], R, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected [From Binder], Sa-Sh, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected [From Binder], Si-So, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected [From Binder], Sp-Sy, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected [From Binder], Ta-To, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected [From Binder], Tr-V, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected [From Binder], W, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected [From Binder], Y-Z, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected Non-Broadcast [From Binder], A-D, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected Non-Broadcast [From Binder], E-N, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Monies Collected Non-Broadcast [From Binder], O-W, Jun 1985-May 1986 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Rates, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Spanish Language Agreement, 1984-1985 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Television Recorded Commercials: Spanish Language Agreement, 1978-1982 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Television Recorded Commercials for 1958-1960 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Transcription Code for 1958-1960 (Ken Groot's Material) (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Transcription for Broadcasting Purposes for 1963-1966 (Ken Groot's Material), 1963-1964 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - UPITN Corporation for 1968-1970 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - UPITN Corporation for 1970-1973 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - UPITN Corporation for 1973-1976: Ken Groot's Working Papers, Apr-Sep 1973 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - UPITN Corporation for 1973-1976: Ken Groot's Working Papers, Oct-Dec 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - UPITN Corporation for 1973-1976: Ken Groot's Working Papers, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - UPITN Corporation for 1976-1978 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - WABC-AM: Authorization for Payment to Artists, 1958-1959 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - WABC-AM for 1969-1972: Staff Announcers, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - WABC-FM for 1969-1972 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - WABC-FM for 1979-1982 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - WABC-FM for 1982-1985, 1983 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - WABC Radio, 1968-1969 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - WABC Radio, 1983 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - WABC Radio: ABC/AFTRA FM Talent Agreement, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - WABC Radio: Program Logs, Mar 1963 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - WABC Radio: Program Logs, Apr 1963 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - WABC, WCBS, WNBC FM for 1973-1976, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - WABC, WCBS, WNBC FM [from Binder] for 1985-1988, 1985-1987 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - WABC, WCBS, WNBC for 1982-1985: Commercial Radio Code, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - WADO for 1961-1963 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - WADO for 1963-1966 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - WADO for 1966-1969, 1966-1968 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - WADO for 1966-1969: Photographs (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - WADO for 1969-1972 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - WADO for 1972-1975, 1972-1974 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - WADO for 1975-1978, 1975-1977 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - WADO for 1978-1981, 1978-1980 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - WADO for 1981-1984, 1981-1982 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - Wages and Working Conditions: Committee, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Wages and Working Conditions: Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Wages and Working Conditions: Committee, Apr-Jul 1982 (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Wages and Working Conditions: Committee (Includes Convention Materials), Aug-Nov 1982 (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - Wages and Working Conditions: Committee, 1983 (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Wages and Working Conditions: Committee, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - Wages and Working Conditions: Contracts, 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 32)
  - Wages and Working Conditions: Contracts, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 33)
  - Wages and Working Conditions: Convention Proposals, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 34)
  - Wages and Working Conditions: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 35)
  - Wages and Working Conditions: Fair Practice Code, 1973-1974 (Box 73, Folder 36)
  - Wages and Working Conditions: Fair Practice Code, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 37)
  - Wages and Working Conditions: Four A's TV Committee, undated (Box 73, Folder 38)
  - Wages and Working Conditions: Proposals, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 39)
  - Wages and Working Conditions: Singers Committee, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - WAPP Radio, 1982-1983 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - WBAI-FM, re: Lorraine Hansbury Tribute, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - WBAI-FM: "Radio Showcase", 1977 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - WBAL-TV/AM/FM, Baltimore, Maryland, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - WBLS-FM for 1974-1976, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - WBLS-FM for 1974-1976 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - WBLS-FM for 1974-1976, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - WBLS-FM for 1976-1978, 1975-1977 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - WBLS-FM for 1978-1980, 1976-1978 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - WBLS-FM for 1978-1979: Dues (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - WBLS-FM for 1978-1980: People Suspended, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - WBLS-FM for 1978-1980: Bob Weiner Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - WBLS-FM for 1978-1980, 1980-1981 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - WBLS-FM for 1980-1983, 1979-1982 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - WBLS-FM for 1980-1983, 1981-1982 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - WBNX-FM for 1970-1971, Jun 1970 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - WBNX-FM for 1970-1971, Jul-Dec 1970 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - WBNX-FM for 1970-1971, Jan-May 1971 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - WBNX-FM for 1970-1971, Jun-Aug 1971 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - WBNX-FM for 1970-1971, Sep-Dec 1971 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - WBNX-FM for 1971-1974, Jan-Feb 1972 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - WBNX-FM for 1971-1974, Apr-Nov 1972 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - WBNX-FM for 1971-1974: Complaints, 1971-1973 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - WBNX-FM for 1971-1974: United Broadcasting v. AFTRA, Apr 22, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - WBNX-FM for 1971-1974, 1974-1975 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - WCBS-AM for 1988-1991, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - WCBS-FM for 1969-1972 (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - WCBS-FM for 1973-1976 (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - WCBS-FM for 1976-1979, 1977-1978 (Box 74, Folder 30)
  - WCBS-FM for 1979-1982 (Box 74, Folder 31)
  - WCBS-FM for 1982-1985, 1982-1983 (Box 74, Folder 32)
  - WCNY-TV, 1983 (Box 74, Folder 33)
  - WERA Radio, Plainfield,New Jersey, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 34)
  - WEVD for 1954-1956 (Box 74, Folder 35)
  - WEVD for 1956-1958 (Box 74, Folder 36)
  - WEVD for 1958-1960, 1957-1958 (Box 74, Folder 37)
  - WEVD for 1960-1963, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 38)
  - WEVD for 1963-1966, 1963-1964 (Box 74, Folder 39)
  - WEVD for 1966-1969, 1966-1967 (Box 74, Folder 40)
  - WEVD for 1969-1972, 1968-1969 (Box 74, Folder 41)
  - WEVD for 1969-1972, 1970-1971 (Box 74, Folder 42)
  - WEVD for 1972-1975, 1972-1973 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - WEVD for 1975-1978, 1974-1977 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - WEVD for 1978-1981, 1978-1979 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - WEVD (later known as WNYM) for 1981-1984, 1980-1981 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - WFAS, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - WFAS, 1956 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - WFAS for 1958-1960 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - WFAS for 1960-1962 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - WFAS for 1962-1964 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - WFAS for 1964-1966 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - WGBB Radio, Freeport, Long Island, 1970-1978 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - WGLI Radio, Babylon, Long Island for 1970-1973, 1971-1972 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - WGLI Radio, Babylon, Long Island for 1973-1976, Jan-May 1973 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - WGLI Radio, Babylon, Long Island for 1973-1976, Jun-Oct 1973 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - WGLI Radio, Babylon, Long Island, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - WGLI Radio, Babylon, Long Island for 1976-1979, 1975-1976 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - WGLI Radio, Babylon, Long Island for 1976-1979: WGLI and Dennis Moore v. AFTRA, 1976-1977 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - WGNR Radio, New Rochelle, 1951-1952 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - WHLI-FM for 1950-1952, 1949-1950 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - WHLI-FM for 1952-1953 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - WHLI-FM for 1953-1956 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - WHLI-FM for 1961-1964, 1959, 1961 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - WHLI-FM for 1964-1967, 1964-1966 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - WHLI-FM for 1967-1970, 1967-1968 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - WHLI-FM for 1970-1973, 1969-1970 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - WHLI [AM] FM for 1973-1977, 1972-1973 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - WHLI [AM] FM for 1973-1977, 1974-1975 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - WHLI [AM, WIOK] FM for 1977-1980, 1976-1977 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - WHLI [AM, WIOK] FM for 1977-1980, 1978-1979 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - WHLI [AM-WKJY FM] for 1980-1983, 1979-1981 (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - WHLI: Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - WHN (WMGM) AM for 1946-1949 (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - WHN (WMGM) AM for 1949-1951, 1950 (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - WHN (WMGM) AM for 1951-1953 (Box 75, Folder 34)
  - WHN (WMGM) AM for 1951-1953, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 35)
  - WHN (WMGM) AM for 1953-1954, Aug-Oct 1953 (Box 75, Folder 36)
  - WHN (WMGM) AM for 1953-1954, Nov-Dec 1953 (Box 75, Folder 37)
  - WHN (WMGM) AM for 1954-1955 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - WHN (WMGM) AM for 1955-1957, 1955-1956 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - WHN (WMGM) AM for 1957-1959, Mar-Sep 1957 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - WHN (WMGM) AM for 1957-1959, Oct-Nov 1957 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - WHN (WMGM) AM [FM] for 1957-1959, 1958 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - WHN (WMGM) AM for 1959-1961 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - WHN (WMGM) AM for 1959-1961, 1960 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - WHN (WMGM) AM for 1961-1963, 1961-1962 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - WHN-AM for 1963-1965 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - WHN-AM for 1963-1965, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - WHN-AM for 1965-1967, Jan-Apr 1965 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - WHN-AM for 1965-1967, May 1965 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - WHN-AM for 1965-1967, Jun-Jul 1965 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - WHN for 1965-1968 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - WHN for 1968-1971, 1967-1968 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - WHN for 1968-1971: Correspondence re: Contracts, 1968-1969 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - WHN for 1968-1971: Correspondence re: Contracts, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - WHN for 1971-1974 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - WHN for 1971-1973: Correspondence re: Contracts (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - WHN for 1971-1973: Correspondence re: Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - WHN-AM for 1974-1977, Jan-Apr 1974 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - WHN-AM for 1974-1977, May-Jul 1974 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - WHN-AM for 1974-1977, Aug-Nov 1974 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - WHN-AM for 1974-1977, 1975-1976 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - WHN-AM: Storer Broadcasting Employee Portfolio for 1974-1977 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - WHN for 1977-1980, Mar 1976-Apr 1977 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - WHN for 1977-1980, May-Dec 1977 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - WHN for 1977-1980, Correspondence re: Contracts (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - WHN for 1977-1980, Correspondence re: Contracts, 1978-1979 (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - WHN for 1980-1983, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - WHN for 1980-1983, Jan-May 1980 (Box 76, Folder 31)
  - WHN for 1980-1983, Jun-Oct 1980 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - WHN for 1980-1983, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - WHN for 1980-1983: Correspondence re. Contracts, 1980-1981 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - WHN for 1980-1983: Correspondence re. Contracts, 1982-1983 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - WHOM Radio for 1967-1970, 1968-1969 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - WHOM Radio: Survey of Spanish Audiences for Negotiations for 1967-1970, 1968-1970 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - WHOM Radio for 1970-1973, 1970-1971 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - WHOM Radio for 1970-1973, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - WHOM Radio for 1973-1976 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - WHOM Radio for 1973-1976, 1974-1975 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - WICC Radio for 1969-1972 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - WICC Radio for 1972-1974, 1972-1973 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - WICC Radio for 1974-1978 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - WICC Radio for 1978-1981, 1979-1982 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - WIGO Radio, Atlanta, Georgia: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - WINS Radio for 1950-1951 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - WINS Radio for 1951-1952 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - WINS Radio for 1952-1953 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - WINS Radio for 1953-1954 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - WINS Radio for 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - WINS Radio for 1955-1956 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - WINS Radio for 1956-1958 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - WINS Radio for 1958-1960 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - WINS Radio for 1958-1961, 1959 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - WINS Radio for 1960-1963, 1959-1960 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - WINS Radio for 1963-1966, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - WINS Radio for 1963-1966, Jan-Feb 1963 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - WINS Radio for 1963-1966, Jun-Aug 1963 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - WINS Radio for 1966-1969, 1965 (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - WINS Radio for 1966-1969, Jan 1966 (Box 77, Folder 30)
  - WINS Radio for 1966-1969, Feb-Mar 1966 (Box 77, Folder 31)
  - WINS Radio for 1966-1969, Aug-Dec 1966 (Box 77, Folder 32)
  - WINS Radio for 1966-1969, 1967 (Box 77, Folder 33)
  - WINS Radio for 1969-1972, 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - WINS Radio for 1969-1972, Jan 1969 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - WINS Radio for 1969-1972, Feb 1969 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - WINS Radio for 1969-1972, Mar-Sep 1969 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - WINS Radio for 1969-1972, 1970 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - WINS Radio for 1972-1975, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - WINS Radio for 1972-1975, Jan 1972 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - WINS Radio for 1972-1975, Feb-Jun 1972 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - WINS Radio for 1975-1978 (Groot's Material), Sep 1974-Jan 1975 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - WINS Radio for 1975-1978, Feb 1-10, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - WINS Radio for 1975-1978, Feb-Aug 1975 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - WINS Radio for 1975-1978: Paste-up of Agreement (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - WINS Radio for 1978-1982 (Groot's Material), Dec 1977-Apr 1978 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - WINS Radio for 1978-1982 (Groot's Material), May-Aug 1978 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - WINS Radio for 1978-1982 (Groot's Material), Oct-Dec 1978 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - WINS Radio 1010 for 1982-1986, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - WINS Radio 1010 for 1982-1986 (Groot's Material), Jan-Mar 1982 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - WINS Radio 1010 for 1982-1986 (Groot's Material), Apr-May 1982 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - WINS Radio 1010 for 1982-1986: AFTRA Proposals (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - WINS Radio 1010 for 1982-1986: Correspondence, Notes, and Related Material, Jan-Feb 1982 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - WINS Radio 1010 for 1982-1986: Correspondence, Notes, and Related Material, Mar 1982 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - WINS Radio 1010 for 1982-1986: Correspondence, Notes, and Related Material, Apr-Dec 1982 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - WINS Radio 1010 for 1982-1986: Correspondence, Notes, and Related Material, 1983 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - WINS Radio 1010 for 1982-1986: Draft Agreement (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - WINS Radio 1010 for 1982-1986: Proposals Settled and Agreed (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - WINS Radio 1010 for 1982-1986: WINS Proposals (Box 78, Folder 26)